He was once a good friend of mine
Eskiden yakındık.
One day, he asked me about a sword art of which he had heard
Bir gün gelip bana bir kılıç sanatı hakkında sorular sordu.
The Musou no Hitotachi
Musou no Hitotachi
I told him
Dedim ki:
It can only be witnessed when "divine punishment" is administered
Yalnızca "ilahi ceza" uygulanırken görebilirsin.
It is the pinnacle of the Raiden Shogun's skill
Şogun Raiden bu konunun ustasıdır.
A symbol of ultimate power
Nihai gücün sembolü...
But he replied: "There must be one who can withstand it"
"Karşı koyabilen biri olmalı" dedi yine de.
"There will always be those who dare to brave the lightning's glow"
"Her daim yıldırımın parıltısına meydan okuyabilecek birileri olacaktır."
Then, the Vision Hunt Decree arrived
Sonra Önsezi Avı Fermanı çıktı.
Peoples' aspirations were stripped away
Şogun Raiden "sonsuzluk" idealini hayata geçirmeye başladıkça
While I was fleeing from place to place
Ben oradan oraya kaçarken
I heard that my friend had challenged the Vision Hunters
bir arkadaşımın Önsezi Avcılarını
To a duel before the throne
saraydaki düelloya davet ettiğini duydum.
A solemn yet brutal challenge
Oldukça ciddi ve bir o kadar da çetin bir meydan okuma.
The defeated face divine punishment, while the victors gain a second chance
Kaybeden ilahi cezaya çarptırılacak ve kazanan da ikinci bir şans elde edecek.
Perhaps he thought he of all people should make a stand
Belki de onca insan arasında boyun eğmeyecek kişinin kendisi olduğunu düşündü.
Coming face to face with the Musou No Hitotachi
Nihayetinde tek istediği şey
When I arrived at Tenshukaku
Tenshukaku'ya vardığımda
The duel was over
düello çoktan bitmişti.
I heard his sentence of divine punishment
İlahi ceza kararını,
His severed blade hitting the ground
kırık kılıcının zemine çarpınca çıkardığı sesi duydum.
Perhaps that was the glory he had yearned to witness
Belki de bu şerefe nail olmak istiyordu.
In his last moments
Son anında
What expression was on his face?
gözlerinde ne gördün?
Before I knew it
Bir anda
I had stepped forward and snatched the dying Vision
oraya atladım ve ölen Önseziyi aldım.
And was running from the scene
Sonra koşarak oradan uzaklaşmaya başladım.
All I knew was that I mustn't let his hope which burned so brightly
Bir umutla yanıp tutuşuyordu ve o an aklımdaki tek şey buna izin vermemekti.